Now we'll study metrics that we can use to evaluate regression models.
现在我们来学习用于评估回归模型的指标
The first one is called mean absolute error.
第一个称为平均绝对误差
In this example we have some points and
在这个示例中 我们有一些点
we have drawn a line that fits these points.
并画了一条拟合这些点的线
Now we would like to check how bad is this line?
现在 我们想检查这条直线的误差如何
A good way to do this is to just add the absolute values
一个好方法就是将点到线的
of the distances from the points to the line.
距离的绝对值求和
Mean absolute error is very easy to calculate in Sklearn.
平均绝对误差在 Sklearn 中很容易计算
What we do in this example is to create a linear regression classifier object,
在这个示例中 我们要做的是创建一个线性回归分类器对象
called classifier.
称为 classifier
Then we use the function to fit the line.
然后用函数来拟合这条直线
Now we can refer to the points as y, and
现在 我们用 y 表示点
to the predictions made by the model as classifier.predict(X).
用 classifier.predict(X) 表示模型所作的预测
We will call this guesses.
称之为 guesses
And finally, the mean absolute error is just calculated
最后 平均绝对误差就用
with the mean absolute error function.
平均绝对误差函数来计算
The mean absolute error has a problem,
平均绝对误差有一个问题
which is that the absolute value function is not differentiable.
即绝对值函数是不可微分的
And this may not be good if we want to use methods such as grading dissent.
这不利于我们使用诸如梯度下降等方法
To solve this problem, we use the more common mean squared error.
要解决这个问题 我们使用更常见的均方误差
For this metric, we add the squares of the distances between the points and
对于此度量 我们添加点和线之间的距离
the line.
的平方
Mean square error is also very easy to calculate in Sklearn,
均方误差也很容易在 Sklearn 中计算
except now we will use the mean_squared_error function.
只是现在 我们要使用 mean_squared_error 函数
Now we will learn a very common regression metric called R2 Score.
现在我们学习一个非常常见的回归度量 称为“R2 分数”
R2 Score is based on comparing our model to the simplest possible model.
R2 分数通过将我们的模型与最简单的可能模型相比得出
So let's think,
那么思考一下
what is the simplest possible model that fits a bunch of points?
拟合一堆点的最简单的可能模型是什么呢？
Well, a pretty simple one is just to take the average of all the values and
那就是取所有值的平均值 然后
draw a horizontal line through them.
画一条穿过它们的水平直线
And then we can calculate the mean squared error for this model.
然后我们可以计算出这个模型的均方误差
We would hope that the mean squared error for
已知 简单模型的均方误差
the simple model is larger than the error for a linear regression model.
大于线性回归模型的误差
The question is, how much larger?
那么问题是大多少？
Well, we can divide the error for
我们可以用线性回归模型的误差
the linear regression model by the error for the simple model, and
除以简单模型的误差 然后
then subtract the result from 1, and we will call this the R2 score.
用 1 减这个结果 我们称之为 R2 分数
If the model is not very good, then the two errors should be similar and
如果这个模型不太好 这两个误差将很接近
this quantity here should be close to one.
而这个量应接近 1
So the whole R2 score should be close to 0.
那么整个 R2 分数应接近 0
If the model is good, then the mean squared error for the linear regression
如果模型较好 那么线性回归模型对的均方误差
model should be a lot smaller than the mean squared error for the simple model.
应比简单模型的均方误差小很多
Therefore this ratio shift is small, and
那么这个比例就很小
then the R2 square should be very close to 1.
而 R2 分数将非常接近 1
In conclusion, if the R2 score is close to 1, then the model is good.
总结来说 如果 R2 分数接近 1 模型就不错
And if it's close to zero, then the model is not much
如果接近 0 那么模型
better than just guessing the average of the values of the points.
基本相当于用点的平均值来猜测
R2 score is very simple to calculate in Sklearn with the R2 score function.
使用 sklearn 中的 r2_score 函数 很容易计算 R2 分数
Here's a small example where we calculated the R2 score between
这里是一个小示例 我们计算了
the true values in blue, and the predicted values in green.
蓝色的真值和绿色的预测值之间的 R2 分数